And today is the fortieth day and I'll
tell you how that day started bro come with me
the piece has arrived,
brother
ok chevos if you don't give work,
didn't see bro
worth it by heart,
saw bro worth it,
worth bro from heaven.
I'm not believing,
just praise that furniture,
bought it on foot if the car doesn't start bro,
now I'm walking again,
the car couldn't solve it.
There's something that looks like it's to test your faith.
I have time to regret it.
I'm really going to walk,
my brother.
I got the address of a nice place to put my truffles and I can't find it,
are you on?
I go by from time to time.
I say hello to you without commitment.
You don't have to worry about stock.
Anything.
We're going to have a meeting tomorrow and then I'll talk about it.
Closed,
closed.
Hi,
Léo is there.
And pleasure,
brother,
be welcome on time.
All right,
guys.
I'm here at Léo's partner tattoo studio.
Another point of sale for truffles.
The Trojan horse fell into the world.
I Leo
anything I send in the zap was worth too much.
Ó tamo together.
1 more old trading post.
What good news on my day.
Oh my hand was tattooed.
Now I'm going to walk all the way back.
Ah,
then you're so good,
Cara.
So I'm putting it in some points of sale.
He got it worth forty truffles.
Can I put it where over there by the box?
Thanks.
You saw my dear old man from heaven bro,
another point of sale for truffles bro,
now the bag is a little mess,
thank God,
bro,
let's go,
let's go.
The customer has nothing to do with it.
With Chevette,
it's got stick.
The result said,
I got two more points of sale.
All because I wasn't telling the sad story,
bro,
I got news here now that it blurred everything bro
Naam naam.